[{"answer": "That's right.", "docId": "110725pmt", "aSentId": 6, "question": "Who is going to blink first?", "qSentId": 5}, {"answer": "It is definitely conceivable.", "docId": "110725pmt", "aSentId": 22, "question": "Is it conceivable that we could get to August the 2nd and a default happens?", "qSentId": 21}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110725pmt", "aSentId": 42, "question": "Can you envisage that kind of scenario?", "qSentId": 41}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110725pmt", "aSentId": 53, "question": "Yes, I mean, Kate Bolduan, let me go to you, because while President Obama was putting his arm around John Boehner and saying, hey, we're great pals, John Boehner was pretty quick to say, get your hands off me, buddy, wasn't he?", "qSentId": 52}, {"answer": "Well, Piers, had these speeches been given three or four weeks ago, I think they would have been welcome as part of the political discourse.", "docId": "110725pmt", "aSentId": 67, "question": "What did they really mean?", "qSentId": 66}, {"answer": "I think probably each fellow came off better in his base.", "docId": "110725pmt", "aSentId": 80, "question": "Has anyone come away better than they did half an hour ago?", "qSentId": 79}, {"answer": "Well, I think there is no doubt that if had just been John Boehner and let's stay the more established Republican leadership, a deal would have been struck.", "docId": "110725pmt", "aSentId": 92, "question": "Can such an intransigent position be helpful to the Republicans right now?", "qSentId": 91}, {"answer": "Well, Piers, no.", "docId": "110725pmt", "aSentId": 110, "question": "Is it?", "qSentId": 109}, {"answer": "Well, I actually -- we were walking out of the room.", "docId": "110725pmt", "aSentId": 121, "question": "What did he make of his golfing partner's comments?", "qSentId": 120}, {"answer": "Listen, there are no off-ramps here.", "docId": "110725pmt", "aSentId": 136, "question": "Is the president prepared to invoke the 14th Amendment and unilaterally raise the debt and simply overrule everyone and go alone?", "qSentId": 135}, {"answer": "Well, listen, we're going to keep making the case, privately and publicly, that compromise is the only option here.", "docId": "110725pmt", "aSentId": 153, "question": "What does the president do?", "qSentId": 152}, {"answer": "Well, I think we ought to avoid that option if we could.", "docId": "110725pmt", "aSentId": 210, "question": "Would you encourage the president to take that option, if all else failed?", "qSentId": 209}, {"answer": "Senator Schumer, thank you.", "docId": "110725pmt", "aSentId": 227, "question": "What more do they want?", "qSentId": 226}, {"answer": "Well, if the team is America, the issue is how to get this economy moving again.", "docId": "110725pmt", "aSentId": 245, "question": "Isn't it time you guys took one for the team, the team being America?", "qSentId": 244}, {"answer": "He did.", "docId": "110725pmt", "aSentId": 260, "question": "He had a point, didn't he, the president, raising that quote?", "qSentId": 259}, {"answer": "Again, I think it's happening.", "docId": "110725pmt", "aSentId": 281, "question": "Are you guys prepared to compromise, as the president asked, and get the deal done?", "qSentId": 280}, {"answer": "Well, I'm opposed to the idea of going bankrupt or hitting the debt ceiling.", "docId": "110725pmt", "aSentId": 333, "question": "You don't want that, do you?", "qSentId": 332}, {"answer": "Well, look, the Republicans would like six trillion dollars in spending restraint over the next ten years.", "docId": "110725pmt", "aSentId": 354, "question": "Who is it going to be?", "qSentId": 353}]